If a certain species of bee disappears forever or a particular plant is extinct, what does that have to do with us humans?
如果某一物种的蜜蜂永远消失，或者某一种特定的植物灭绝了，这与我们人类有什么关系呢？
Well, according to a group of international scientists, biodiversity is dropping to levels below what is considered safe for the wellbeing of human societies.
嗯，根据一组国际科学家的研究，生物多样性正在降至被认为对人类社会福祉安全的水平以下。
The issue is that everything is interconnected and ecosystems support our societies because they provide us with, for example, food, fibres and fuels.
问题在于，万物都是相互关联的，生态系统支撑着我们的社会，因为它们为我们提供了食物、纤维和燃料等。
If species go on disappearing, this can interfere with vital processes such as crop pollination and the decomposition of waste.
如果物种继续消失，这可能会干扰诸如农作物授粉和废物分解等重要过程。
A framework which defines the environmental limits within which humans can operate - called planetary boundaries - says that losing more than 10% of the biodiversity in an area places the local ecosystem at risk.
一个定义了人类活动的环境限度的框架——被称为地球界限——指出，一个地区失去超过10%的生物多样性会使当地的生态系统处于危险之中。
Ecosystems are all different but this percentage is considered a good measure of safety.
生态系统各不相同，但这个百分比被认为是衡量安全性的一个良好指标。
A study published in the magazine Science suggests that 58% of the world's land surface already falls below this level.
发表在《科学》杂志上的一项研究表明，世界上58%的地表面积已经低于这个水平。
These areas house 71% of the global population.
这些地区居住着全球71%的人口。
Professor Andy Purvis, from Imperial College London and the Natural History Museum, is one of the authors of the study.
来自伦敦帝国理工学院和自然历史博物馆的安迪·珀维斯教授是这项研究的作者之一。
He says: "Once we're the wrong side of the boundary it doesn't mean everything goes wrong immediately, but there is a markedly higher risk that things will go badly wrong."
他说：“一旦我们越过了这条界限，并不意味着一切会立即出错，但事情严重出错的风险会显著增加。”
The researchers found that grasslands, savannas and shrub lands were most affected by biodiversity loss on average.
研究人员发现，平均而言，草原、稀树草原和灌木丛受生物多样性丧失的影响最大。
Purvis hopes this report can be a wake-up call to those who design policies.
珀维斯希望这份报告能给那些制定政策的人敲响警钟。
Here's his warning: "Decision-makers worry a lot about economic recessions, but an ecological recession could have even worse consequences - and the biodiversity damage we've had means we're at risk of that happening.
他警告说：“决策者们非常担心经济衰退，但生态衰退可能会带来更严重的后果——而我们已经造成的生物多样性破坏意味着我们正面临着这种情况发生的风险。
Until and unless we can bring biodiversity back up, we're playing ecological roulette."
除非我们能够恢复生物多样性，否则我们就是在玩生态轮盘赌。”